How many people have
been to Coachella?
Oh, my God, we got to
do a field trip, Mike.
Yeah OK.
Maybe final project.
Surprise project.
Yeah, off campus field trip.
So usually, when you go to
a concert, for those of you,
we will make sure that you
get to a concert, a real one.
When you have a headliner,
you need an opening act,
to warm up the audience.
And so today, I'm
your opening act
for the rest of this quarter.
We're going to have Mike,
in the coming weeks as well,
who's going to be
doing a deep dive
into a bunch of confidential
computing stuff.
But I'm here to give you some
context about the speakers
and the rest of the class.
And then we're going to
do a bit of a deep dive
into the area of the world
I understand most, which
is compute infrastructure.
But both today and for
the rest of this quarter,
these really are
your headliners.
Yeah.
Make sense?
You recognize some
of these names?
All right.
Yeah.
For the ones you
don't recognize,
I would recommend
looking them up
because over the
next few years you're
going to hear about
them a lot more.
One extra thing, we are
considering because many of you
asked, given the insane
amount of demand we've had,
both from speakers,
as well, you guys.
To add more topics
and more coverage,
we might add a virtual
office hours every Friday
from noon to 2 PM.
Especially for speakers who are
zooming in from around the world
and can't make it in person.
That will be optional,
extra credit.
A quick show of hands.
How many people would
actually like that?
OK, I guess we ought
to do it, Mike.
All right.
Cool.
More details coming.
More work.
This is the swag for this class.
I forget who it was, but
somebody sent me a tweet.
Apparently there was a tweet
that went viral yesterday
about this class that said,
be wary of taking classes
that sound like AI Coachella.
And there's lots more serious AI
classes on campus you can take.
Totally agree.
And by the way, I thought
that was pretty fun.
I think Coachella is pretty fun.
So as you guys, I did
my undergrad here,
I did grad school.
And look, I think we're
going to be talking
a lot about technical
stuff, but we also
get to talk in this class
about life and leadership.
And so, I thought before we
jump in to technical stuff,
we talked a lot about
scaling laws last time,
and we're going to talk a lot
about that in this quarter.
But I thought I'll give you a
little preview into Anj's life
scaling laws.
I think that you should
take life seriously.
But not so seriously that
you forget what's important.
Don't forget how to
have fun and remember
what makes life worth living.
Because look now, you might
feel like you have all the time
in the world, and
sometimes you don't
know when you don't have
much more time left.
So enjoy it while you can.
Don't take for granted.
It's a really magical time
you guys are in right now.
My view is it's very
simple actually,
to live life and scale yourself.
Scale your impact, which I
know many of you want to do.
A lot of times, a lot
of the students we've
taught over the last few years,
have come to office hours
and asked, Anj, Mike,
you've been so successful,
blah, blah, blah.
How do you plan your future?
It's very similar to how
do you plan a training run.
You want to really knock it out
of the park on capabilities.
You want to scale
capabilities and revenue,
like we talked about last time.
And it's hard to
forecast these things.
So I've actually found a
pretty simple heuristic
on how to navigate that
journey, which is just
have fun with people you
enjoy hanging out with.
That's pretty much it.
I found empirically,
remember we talked
about how scaling laws are
empirical, not predictive.
I found empirically, that's
worked out pretty well.
So if there's one thing I'd
love for you all to take away
from this quarter, this
is the last lecture,
I'm going to be
giving this quarter.
We have lots of
speakers and so on.
But I just want to
leave you with this one.
Which is, the most important
people in this class
aren't really my
committee or the speakers.
It's you guys.
Look around and see
how special it is.
Really invest in
these relationships
because you won't
realize how they come in
and help you out in all
kinds of ways in life.
As you guys saw, I met my
wife here as a sophomore.
Say hi, Viv.
We've been together 13 years.
As I mentioned, I have
started two companies,
both with former
roommates from Stanford.
One of them is my current 1 Amp.
The world is a messy place.
It can seem like there's a
lot of crazy stuff happening
in the world.
We're fighting wars.
There's a lot of
violence, a lot of chaos.
But you guys are in a very
special moment in time.
Just think about
all the things that
had to come together for all of
you to be sitting in this room.
So just, generally see,
how special and lucky
you are to be here.
And we talked last time
about how it can feel.
I think somebody
asked, I forget who
it was, who asked the question.
With all these AI labs
and big companies spending
so much on AI and
infrastructure,
how could we possibly create
something interesting or novel
or new in science
and engineering?
And remember I said, use them.
Do things that don't scale or
be asymmetric about your bets.
And one of those is,
obsess over the things
you love because there's some
things that don't scale well,
especially in large
organizations.
And so throughout this quarter,
just remember that you actually
do have some special weapons.
And one of those is, the
obsessions, the love,
the trust you have for each
other, the friendships,
the relationships
you'll build here
and over the next few
years, because that
will come in very handy.
And it'll be things,
those kinds of things,
are assets that don't scale,
as you join larger and larger
companies or organizations.
OK, I'll stop
being an uncle now,
and I will say, maybe
go to the real Coachella
while you still can.
One of my biggest regrets
is when I was in campus,
we were working so
hard and staying
so focused on projects
and coursework,
I've never been to
Coachella, it turns out.
And so maybe we will
go with you guys.
Shall we proceed?
Yes OK.
Thank you guys.
Quick recap.
Yeah for those of you who are
joining us for the first time.
I'm Anj, I'm one of
your co instructors.
There's Mike.
He's going to introduce himself
during his lecture as well.
My full name is pronounced
Anjani, friends call me Anj.
I was born in India.
Went to high school
in Singapore.
Came over for college, here
at Stanford many years ago.
And then I ended up staying.
This is now my home.
I live in San Francisco, with
my wife, in Presidio Heights.
And you guys are all welcome
to come by anytime you'd like.
I've been in love with applied
machine learning for the better
part of the last 15 years.
I came here as an undergrad.
I took a bunch of
coursework in economics
and a major that I don't
think exists anymore,
called mathematics and
computational science.
And then for grad school,
I did bio-informatics
over at the med school,
which is essentially machine
learning applied to health.
I've always been a
very applied thinker.
I've always found that
it's really exciting
to look at what machine
learning systems, when taken out
into the real world at scale,
can tell you about the world.
Which is often
actually a pattern
you see, not just in computer
science, but in physics.
Physics is about trying to
understand how the world works,
looking at large
patterns empirically,
trying to figure out are
there laws we can derive
about the world.
This is the applied physics part
of the discipline, of course,
and I still actually spend
some of my time on campus
at the Physics Department
as a visiting scientist.
Where we've been doing a bunch
of benchmarking on frontier
models and how they're good
or not, at physics and science
reasoning.
Feel free to ask me
about that any time we'll
have office hours.
I've had a chance over
the last 10 to 15 years
to invest, co-found, or be part
of the early days of over 10 AI
labs.
Some of those you guys
know, Anthropic, Mistral,
Black Forest.
You'll be hearing from many
of these in this class.
And as we just talked
about, I have a deep, deep.
I'm deeply thankful for what
Stanford has done for me.
Sometimes I shitpost on Twitter.
Don't believe everything
you read on Twitter.
But if you're ever wondering
what my shower thoughts are,
that's where you can find me.
My handle is Anjani Mehta.
If you guys remember.
For those of you who
were here last time,
this is a cheat code to
the rest of the class.
And I think the rest of the
next two years, at least
in the industry
outside of Stanford.
OK, this is not
just a CS 153 thing.
Hopefully this
will give you a bit
of a framework for how to
navigate life after college.
Because if you
remember, we talked
about the goal of this class is
preparedness for the real world.
The goal is not internships.
The goal is preparedness.
What is happening in the
infrastructure world.
In the CS systems world, we are
going through a massive change
over the last 10, 15 years.
With the rise of
distributed systems,
cloud infrastructure,
a somewhat stable stack
had emerged, about how we
create, ship and scale software.
And these are the
different layers
of the stack that
I would roughly
say dominate the industry.
We start with capital,
which is quite flexible.
You can put money in everything.
Then you have land power shell,
energy production, data centers,
construction, on top of that.
Or in the data
centers, you put chips,
you then have some
software infrastructure,
called a cloud that
makes those chips usable.
And then you start.
We hook up all these
chips together.
We train a model.
Sometimes we call them agents.
We then put them
into an application,
we deploy them as solutions.
And then lastly, we
try to figure out
how to actually
govern these things.
What's the safety, the security,
the trust, the frameworks?
We need to actually make sure
that these technologies get
deployed to the real world.
When Mike and I started
this class 4 years ago,
it was called Security at Scale.
At the time I was running
the platform org at Discord.
How many people have
heard of Discord?
Perfect.
We did our jobs.
And Mike was running
infrastructure
at Apple at the time.
And both of us had started
to realize that security
was becoming an increasingly
critical topic in the world,
but there just weren't that
many places for people like you
guys to learn what the
frontier, what the cutting edge
problems of security were.
Because you don't get
to see those on campus.
And so this class started
as the missing systems
class, that I wish had existed
when I was an undergrad.
And so, that's where
this all started.
Since then it's evolved.
We started with 50 students.
We're now 500.
Thank you all for joining us.
I think we have another 50
wait-listed and a few thousand
people following online.
I'm not sure when else we'll
get to teach this class again.
So let's try to
make the most of it.
Yeah.
OK.
We're going through
the great transition,
because we have this
new technology called
AI that has unlocked,
extraordinary value
and is about to
unlock way more value.
Everybody, every leader
or every major team,
or, I would say, people who care
about the future at every layer
of the stack are wondering, how
do we unblock the bottlenecks?
How do we make this stuff
go faster and safer and more
secure?
And what we're learning
in the industry,
is that it takes revisiting
a lot of basic assumptions
about how the stack works, where
in the value chain you are,
what your job is, what
your technical function is,
what your economic function is.
And I think you
will start to see,
you probably
already are feeling,
what I'm calling the
great transition.
Driven by this urgent need
across all levels of society.
You saw the diversity
in names we have.
We have people like
Jensen Huang and Lisa Su,
at the chip layer coming
in to talk to you guys.
We have folks like Satya
Nadella who runs Microsoft,
who's at the cloud layer.
We have Sam Altman.
How many people
have heard of Sam?
Sam Altman, yeah, there we go.
OK.
He's coming by to
talk about models
and how they're deploying stuff.
So this is a really big
shift that's happening.
For the first time,
at least in my life,
I can't remember a time when
there was such a big revisiting
of assumptions up
and down the stack,
where everyone's trying
to figure something out.
And that's really
cool, because that
creates an extraordinary amount
of opportunity for you guys,
because in times of uncertainty,
That's when things change.
And people who understand
where the world is going,
who have a point of
view, get to redesign
the systems that have stayed
quite static in the past.
OK.
I don't what the new world
is going to look like.
I don't think anybody does.
But for the next
10 weeks, you are
going to hear from
some of the most,
I think, dynamic, talented
and capable leaders
reasoning through how to unblock
the bottlenecks at each part
of this ecosystem every week.
Cool.
Sound good?
Should we keep going?
OK.
No, you don't need to
clap for me every time.
Don't worry, I got it.
Let me earn my keep.
So quick recap.
Remember, we said what is
going on at the frontier.
What is this whole thing
called intelligence?
And a few years ago, when
I was starting to get
calls from friends who had
gone to grad school with
or we're running research
at places like OpenAI.
I started getting
calls saying, oh, we
think there's an
opportunity to really take
some of this research
out of the lab
and turn it into products and
services that could impact
hundreds of millions of people.
And at the time, it was a
pretty craft, bespoke process.
And we talked last time, about
pretty simple recipe on how
to manufacture intelligence.
Compute, data, algorithms.
Pretty simple algorithm
transformer, do
a little bit of pre-training,
some fine tuning.
Good to go.
Plug it into an app.
You got ChatGPT.
We're going to have Liam Fedus,
the co-creator of ChatGPT,
come by and talk to you
guys later this quarter.
Things look very different now.
In four short years, we've taken
what was a pretty, I would say,
bespoke process and turned it
into an industrial engineering
process at scale.
Back then, three
or four years ago,
the frequency of
creating a new model
was maybe once a
year, twice a year.
And today we have this
industrial scale production
process where we do
base model training,
at least two times a year on
100,000 GB, B 300 equivalents.
And then we do post training
with about 10% of that compute.
So mid training we add more
capabilities into that.
And that happens about 2 to four
times a year, with about 10%
of that compute.
And then we do this thing
called continuous post training.
Right?
With supervised
fine tuning and RL.
And I won't bore you
with all the details
that we talked about last time.
We'll have assigned readings.
Slides will be up.
But I'll let you
guys go do the math
on how much compute and money
is being spent on these systems.
What's the most
recent, of course,
development in all of this.
Is that the last mile of this,
the reinforcement learning part,
is now consuming
almost as much compute
as all of the rest of
the pipeline combined.
And that's very exciting
Because one, it's new.
But it also means that
things are changing fast
and resources and strategies
are consolidating.
And so our hope over
the next 10 weeks
is that you get a bit of a
window of a front row seat
into that part of the ecosystem.
OK.
So what does all this mean
actually for progress?
This is where we
stopped last time.
And this is where I'm
going to pick up today.
A quick disclosure list.
And any good scientist,
you start by disclosing
the experiments you've run.
This is a list of teams that
I've had a chance, AI lab teams
that I've had a
chance to work with.
Many of these were literally
co-authors on a paper
that then we teamed up on, to
turn into a company or a project
out in the real world.
Some of them, I was involved
in as an angel investor,
some as a co-founder.
And you'll hear from
many of these people
over the rest of this quarter.
But this is also
disclosure list.
I am biased,
naturally, when you're
observing an
empirical experiment,
you are naturally biased by
the data that you're fed.
And so between Mike and
myself, what we've tried to do,
is at least augment
our individual biases
and work experiences with a
diverse set of as uncorrelated,
of a set of perspectives for
you all across the ecosystem
as we could in 10 short weeks.
So this is the
crux of the class.
Of this lecture.
What are the bottlenecks
on these capabilities?
Many of you are excited
about these capabilities,
I certainly am.
As we talked about last time,
you can use them for everything
from having a conversation
when you're by yourself,
doing your homework.
That use case is banned for
this one, for this class though.
If you do use any of the coding
models for your assignments,
just tell us about them.
That's all fine.
But it's a pretty diverse,
it's a pretty general purpose
technology.
I found these foundation
models, and so for the next,
let's say 40 minutes or so,
what I'm going to try to do,
is break down in detail at a
systems level, what is going on.
And what, in terms of
the inputs required
to keep these models
and these systems
continuing their blistering
pace of progress.
So we can all benefit, apply
this incredible technology
beyond chatbots to new areas,
like curing novel diseases,
discovering new materials.
I'm of the opinion that
there's an extraordinary number
of new frontiers to be
explored and developed with AI,
but it's not going to happen
without us as a society,
figuring out how to unblock
progress in all the domains
that we care about.
OK, again, the recipe
is pretty simple.
I'm going to break
down the bottlenecks
into four major areas context,
compute, capital, and culture.
And we'll see how much we
can reason through this.
Today I'm going to start
with context and compute
and then we'll go from there.
OK.
Might have to do an
extra overflow office
hours or something.
OK.
Context.
A couple of prereqs you're
going to need, to understand
the next few slides.
Reinforcement learning,
very simple technique,
super powerful.
Driving a ton of the progress
at the frontier today.
We talked about it last time.
If you've had a pet, or you've
had a sibling who you've
had to teach to stay
away from your room,
you are a successful
frontier model trainer.
Applying reinforcement learning.
The key idea is that when you
have a system that you want
to improve at a
given set of tasks,
you don't tell the agent
or the model how to do it.
You just tell it what to do,
what task you want to reward.
And when it completes
that successfully,
you give it a reward.
If it doesn't do
it successfully,
you withhold the reward and
then you rinse and repeat.
Very simple idea, has been
around for a long time.
Started really working, I
would say, in earnest at scale
about two years ago.
And that was because
when you initialize
a reinforcement
learning environment
with an agent like LLM,
that's smart enough,
has smart enough priors
about the real world.
It turns out that these systems
learn much faster than usual,
and the capabilities
tend to continue scaling
the more compute
we throw at them,
and the more of environmental
harnesses and contexts
we give them.
Which is pretty
novel, pretty new.
Earlier, over the last 70
years of computer science,
as we discussed about the
bitter lesson in lecture one.
RL would plateau pretty
fast in different domains.
Chess, Go, et cetera.
It would surpass
human performance,
but then the rate of
progress would plateau.
And the reason it
seems again, this is, I
would say an open
area of debate,
is that the priors, the previous
inbuilt reasoning capabilities
of the models, were
just not general enough
to continue learning in
a scence after a while.
You guys, you've
heard the phrase,
you can't teach an
old dog new tricks?
Whereas it turns out,
you can sometimes
teach a Stanford student to
come back and teach new classes.
This is my dad joke
kicking in as well.
I'll try to stay
away from the puns.
So this is the core
philosophical tension of RL,
It's working much
better than expected.
It seems to be because LLMs
have enabled a new era where
the models, the language models,
are smart enough to then give us
new capabilities.
When you use post-training
to improve them
on some specific task,
benchmark or capability.
Making sense?
Everybody following me?
No?
OK.
We might have to
do an RL tutorial,
but I would encourage
you to, how many people
have taken a machine learning
class at Stanford already?
OK.
Keep your hands up.
How many of you
have at least done
one P set with an RL problem?
OK.
That's the issue.
All right.
We're going to have
about 30% or so.
We'll do an office
hours on that.
And you're going to have
some of the co-inventors,
some of the pioneers around
RL actually come talk to you.
So they'll probably do
a better job than me.
But to recap, where does
this fit in to what's
going on in the industry?
As we talked about last time.
I got a call from some
friends, Daria and Tom, who
are running research at OpenAI.
Four years ago
they said, we want
to leave and start a new lab.
Can we figure out how to
build a business around this?
And so we spent some
time fleshing out
how do we turn the scaling of
capabilities into a business.
And this was the simple
recipe we came up with.
Raise some money,
buy some compute,
augment it with data, pre-train.
Put out a model that's good
enough, considered state
of the art, that some people,
like programmers, want
to use them.
Deploy it, do inference, run
the model and that gives you
two loops.
The inference hopefully
gives you enough money
to buy your next
round of compute
and gives you context feedback.
You can observe in the
case of a pair programmer,
when is the model
actually accomplishing
the task you want it to or not.
It has your monorepo, your
git history, your local files.
And then you pipe that
back, we call that context.
The context feedback loop
back through RL, hundreds
and thousands of times as
many times as you need.
With as much
compute as you need,
to improve the capabilities
of that system in that domain.
Pretty simple recipe.
As I discussed last time,
we made 22 introductions.
I was an angel investor
at the time in Anthropic,
made 22 introductions to friends
up and down Sand Hill Road.
They came back with 21 no's.
And a lot of them just said, it
sounds theoretically cool Anj,
as an idea, but do you
have any empirical proof?
Do you have proof?
Well, as you guys four years
later, we do have proof.
I won't bore you
with all the slides
we talked about last time
with the Anthropic revenue,
et cetera.
I think we do have one slide
later when we talk about
compute, so I'll
come back to that.
But to fast forward now.
I think if you believe
that recipe works.
Anthropic has gone from 9
to 20 billion in revenue.
Gemini is doing well.
OpenAI started to produce
extraordinary revenue.
There's lots of proof
that this recipe works.
The question I keep
getting over and over again
is, well who wins?
Who wins in this?
If everybody's going to be
applying this scaling recipe
and it's so easy and
repeatable, then where
does the value accrue?
And at least one
opinion I started
to observe through all those
empirical experiments I talked
about with you guys earlier, is
that context is critical here.
Context or the
environment of the agent.
We talked, if you're
training your dog,
it's to fetch in a park.
That park is the context.
It's the environment.
All the people in
the park, the kids
that may be running around
the grass, the physics of rain
coming down.
All of those factors
of the environment,
influence the ability for
you to improve and train
your system, your
pet, to perform better
and better in the real world.
And so I find myself explaining
this pretty frequently to folks,
and I hope it'll make sense
to you, is that one, where?
To answer the question of
where will Frontier progress
continue most rapidly?
And this is relevant
for all of your projects
because many of you
must be going, OK.
Coding seems to be
well on its way,
and image generation is
also well on its way.
You have Andreas from
Black Forest labs,
who created Stable
Diffusion, but where else
can I make a difference?
And one question I
would ask is, well,
where is their
context that can be
reliably measured
and verified when
you're working with an agent?
And I think wherever in
life we have verifiability,
code is verifiable.
You can write unit tests and
your code passes it or not.
Material science, it turns
out, is quite verifiable.
Again, you will hear
from Liam and DOGE
at Periodic Labs
about how they're
using RL from
physical verification
to discover new superconductors.
Very cool stuff.
There's a bunch of robots at
a 30,000 square foot facility
in Menlo Park nearby, that maybe
we do a field trip or something.
But where else is the
context and the environment
capable of verifying the
accuracy of the task as
performed by the agent?
That's the question I would
be asking if I was you.
The second question
that falls out from that
is, well, who's going
to capture that value?
Because you don't want
to just be researchers.
You guys actually want to do
sustainable frontier system
development.
Not just one off model drops.
You want to scale these things.
OK.
Well, it's the
teams that will have
unique and defensible
access to some context,
if you get there first.
Or maybe you have some insight.
That's where teams will, I
think, capture the most value.
So those are the teams I
think are going to win.
And then who's going to lose?
My view is that the
teams that get locked out
of contexts that are essential
to improve these models,
and the capabilities on some
domain, will not have a chance.
Now to bring that
to life, I thought
I'd just give you a
few examples right
of this context, these
context loop wars beginning.
I think just about a year
ago, there was a news drop
that OpenAI tried to acquire
an IDE, that many of you
probably use for your
coding work called Windsurf.
How many people have
heard of windsurf?
Oh, OK.
Cool
I mean, we'll be happy
to hear about that.
A few days later after it
was announced that Windsurf
was being acquired by OpenAI.
Anthropic shut off model
access to Windsurf users,
doesn't happen often.
We don't in our industry.
We don't usually shut off an
API to users without warning.
But it made total sense.
Because if your
competitor needs access
to your model, the
context and can
distill from observing how you
help out customers that you
want to attack, that's leakage.
You have context leakage there.
And so to those of
us in the industry,
this was very clear to me.
It was very normal.
I was not surprised, but I
think for a lot of people
started updating their
mental model again.
Remember that stack diagram?
If your a model provider and
then your application company,
you can always rely
on your model company
to keep giving you intelligence.
Well, that was one assumption
that stopped scaling then.
OK.
And this is happening across the
economy in different contexts,
whether it's consumers,
creators, companies, countries,
and every part of the economy.
There's a battle that's raging
for these context feedback
loops.
And over the next
10 weeks, you're
going to hear from
many of these people.
In fact, you're going
to hear opposing views.
And that's our job
here as instructors.
Our job is not to try to
convince you of our views.
It's to try and educate you,
with an independent view
as much as possible,
so you can derive
the conclusions you believe
about where the future is going.
Because look, this
is an open problem.
Again, we're running
the grand experiment
of how to keep frontier
progress going around the world.
It's making sense?
Yes?
OK.
Good, people are nodding.
Can I hear a yes?
OK.
Thank you.
So let's deep dive for a
second in one of these.
How many people
have heard of Lama?
Great.
One of the creators
of Llama, was a guy
by the name of Guillaume
Lample, who spoke in our class
last year.
His lectures up on YouTube.
Go check it out.
Guillaume and his
college friend,
Arthur Mensch, who is going to
be speaking here in a few weeks,
teamed up a few years ago.
Arthur was a
researcher at DeepMind.
He was one of the lead authors
on a paper called Chinchilla.
Chinchilla Scaling Laws, have
been assigned as reading.
So a good professor,
never asks if the students
have done the reading.
I'm going to assume
you guys have.
Good faith.
Honor code.
Definitely read that
before Arthur shows up.
It'll tell you a
lot about his view.
But Mistral was a new frontier
lab started in Europe,
by the co-creators of
Llama and Chinchilla,
and their view was very simple.
They said, hey, there's going
to be an extraordinary amount
of progress in
closed source models
because that context is
just not that sensitive.
And people won't mind piping
their software engineering
context if you're a
developer in Silicon Valley,
to a cloud server somewhere.
But if it's a mission
critical context,
what they call the
sovereign context,
it matters to a government.
It's national records,
defense and so on.
Well, you need to start
locking that down locally.
And that means you need
models and weights that
run locally on
your infrastructure
that you can control.
And so they started Mistral
as a way for companies
or organizations that needed
control over their own context
to deploy models.
Open source models locally.
And the reason I think
this is worth talking about
is because it's quite hard, in
the world of infrastructure,
especially software
infrastructure,
to beat the relentless
flywheel of the decreasing
marginal cost of production
in storage, in networking
and servers.
The history of cloud
over the last 15 years
has basically been
decreasing marginal cost.
When Amazon and Google, who both
had extraordinary businesses
serving consumers.
Google and search.
Amazon and shopping.
They were just piling
up lots and lots
of servers for their own needs.
And they started realizing, hey
it doesn't cost that much for us
to add another server and
another server, another server,
and basically just rent
that out to other people.
Because at some point, the scale
of your own first party needs
is so high, that you can pass
on the benefits of that scale
to third parties.
And that's how we
got AWS, GCP, Azure.
Mike helped start Azure.
Sorry to date you, Mike.
But that's basically 15 years
of relentless consolidation
in the cloud infrastructure
world because
of the economies of scale.
For the first time in 15
years, that's changing.
Why do you have President
Macron, the head of a country,
and Jensen, the
world's richest man,
or was I think last quarter,
probably still is showing up
on stage in Paris, next
to a 33-year-old scientist
who's never run a
business before?
Saying this is the
future of Europe.
It's because of context.
There are governments and
mission critical workloads
that are just too sensitive to
be run on cloud infrastructure
overseas.
We talked last year in the
class about the CLOUD Act.
How many people have
heard of the CLOUD Act?
OK.
0.
We've got to assign
that as reading.
The CLOUD Act is
policy that says
that if you're running workloads
on United States servers,
whether or it's a company or
it's servers run by a United
States company, globally, the
government has the ability
to access that data.
To some people around
the world that's not OK.
And so now suddenly AI workloads
have gone from being cool,
chat bot assistants, to being
mission critical systems.
Remember we talked about RL?
RL has started to work with a
level of precision and accuracy
in mission critical context.
And that's why you have a
huge reshuffling of cloud
infrastructure globally.
And you'll start to hear
this word sovereign AI
and infrastructure
independence a lot
more over the next few years.
OK.
Just to wrap that
point, that's what's
allowing startups to un-bundle
monopolies in the infrastructure
world or let me call
them oligopolies,
because some of our
guests won't be happy
when I say monopolies at scale.
At speed and scale.
And this is very
exciting because you guys
get to participate in
this revolution, too.
And so one clue you could have
about where to spend your time,
is where there's a
unique context that
hasn't been available to you
because you're not at scale.
But that you can
do something unique
and get ahead of and
start being a participant
in that restructuring
of that industry.
Make sense?
Yes?
Come on, guys, it's spring.
Yes.
OK.
Thank you.
So how do you actually
get this going?
After doing this for 10
years and mostly five
of intense investing,
company co-founding.
Nowadays people call me
the founding investor.
Basically means I'm neither
the CEO, which is all many
of the talented folks
I get to work with,
who are usually scientists.
But I'm not a traditional
venture capitalist.
I don't really write a check.
I typically co-found
these companies on day one
with these teams, and I
do this one at a time.
My current project is Periodic
Labs as we've talked about,
but I've observed a pattern
over and over again.
Which is, you formulate a
state of the art mission.
What is a frontier that
we really want to advance?
Material science, coding,
whatever it might be,
and that you make
that your mission.
We want to move the frontier.
We want to create state
of the art intelligence
in a particular domain.
You then get enough compute.
That's research compute.
You do some experiments, you
figure out how can we actually
get something novel out to
the world that doesn't exist,
and often in a new domain.
That's actually not that hard
to do because we're early,
ship it, get it out into a
context that you have access to,
run the feedback loop.
And then remember we talked
about that scaling, those two
flywheels.
Then just keep them going.
Keep them going
as long as you can
because that is the gift that
keeps giving because they
reinforce each other.
Eventually, at some point when
these flywheels get good enough,
they start propelling
themselves.
That's what many
people in the industry
call recursive self-improvement.
Sometimes people like to call
this the path to AGI or ASI.
Well, I'm an infrastructure
guy, so I think more
at the level of the system.
I don't necessarily think
in terms of a model,
but you can often have a
company hitting takeoff
because they've just figured
out as a good execution team
and how to keep recursively
improving themselves.
It doesn't have to be an actual
model that's super intelligent
or whatever.
I mean, that's one view.
That's fine.
You guys should ask our speakers
if that's how they view it.
But I think about
recursive self-improvement
at the systems level.
That's attacking the
state of the art mission,
not really at an individual
model or API level.
So the big question
where does this
leave us on the context question
is, what are the limits to RL?
And this is a very
exciting open question.
I hope this will be
answered over my lifetime.
It may not be I don't how
much time we have to really
figure this out, but
there's two views on it
today, that I hear
in the industry.
One is a philosophical, the
other is the empirical view.
The philosophical view is that
hey, given the right context,
given sufficient
compute, these agents
should be able to
learn anything.
So once you get that
recursive takeoff happening,
why don't you just ask
the agent to construct,
if you have a coding
agent and the coding agent
is not very good at
material science.
But at some point,
if it's good enough,
you just tell the coding agent,
please build yourself a material
science environment and then
go do the RL loop yourself,
and so on and so forth.
That's one view.
It's not clear right now to me
that RL is generalizing outside
of task distributions, which
means outside of the domain
that you started that frontier
flywheel in the context
feedback.
It's not clear to me that models
are generalizing from let's say,
coding to material science
to biology, et cetera.
I think within the narrow
distribution of coding
and so on, what we're seeing, is
basically relentless progress.
It doesn't look like it's
stopping anytime soon.
And look, this is a big
area of debate, billions
of dollars being invested
in trying to figure
the answer to this question.
My view is closer to
the second one, which
is that empirically, what I've
observed, is that life is messy.
Progress is fastest in,
easily verifiable domains.
And so in domains like
coding which is verifiable,
you will start to see the idea
of a narrow superintelligence or
exponential progress.
But in areas in the world
where progress is not
as easily verifiable.
And a great example of that
is aesthetics, beauty, love.
What are these?
How do you verify?
What is a good verifiable
construct for beauty or love
or aesthetics?
How many of you have
tried writing a message
to your friend, like an
extended blog post or something
with Claude or ChatGPT?
Only four or five people.
OK.
Clearly you guys
have real work to do.
Unlike me.
Writing blogs all the time.
It's terrible.
These models are not good
at long form writing.
At creative writing,
they hallucinate,
they make these clichéd
hyphens and so on.
You see the M dashes
and the, it's not.
This is a game changer.
Ever heard of that phrase
It's not just x, it's y?
I sent a blog post.
I was writing, like a bit of a
manifesto about infrastructure
to a friend three
weeks ago, who's
a founder you'll hear
from in this class said,
can I get your
sanity check on it?
He writes back in 30 seconds,
did you use Claude for this?
I was like, no.
He's like, I don't believe you.
Well, it turns out I had
written the outline myself,
and then I'd asked
Claude to flesh it out.
We've all done it.
And he could tell immediately.
And since then, we have
an internal rule at AMP.
We don't send each other
AI generated documents.
We think, we sit, we write,
and we share with each other,
even if it's raw.
So many of the speakers
you're going to hear from,
working, in the model
level are innovating here,
trying to answer this question.
And I'd encourage you to
do some research on them.
A lot of people share openly
about their strategies online.
So do your homework,
come prepared.
Push them on these questions.
Yeah.
The more you prep you
do, the more work,
the more value you're going
to get out of these lectures.
And more importantly, I think
you guys can innovate here too,
because it's early and
there's so many domains
that maybe you understand
and only you can verify.
Because of your obsession,
your love, your taste,
your sense of
beauty, your culture.
And I think that's the
most valuable thing
you could be doing.
When I get a call
from a new team that
wants me to invest or help them
build a business, what I'm often
looking for is, what
is the unique frontier
that they can
verify for humanity?
I had one of my favorite, he
might not like me sharing this,
but I'll share it
anyway and we'll publish
after getting his permission.
How many people here have heard
of the YouTube channel, 3 Blue 1
Brown?
Whoa.
OK.
I did not realize.
I'm going to have to call Grant.
Grant Sanderson, who is the
creator of 3 Blue 1 Brown, and I
were undergrad drawmates.
He lived in Frosoco.
I lived in Uj.
There were four of us
who were good friends.
And then we drew into
Crothers together.
Yeah.
Crothers.
But Grant and I have stayed
in touch over the years.
And he came by.
He crashed over at my house
for the last two days,
and he unfortunately had to
fly out this morning at 6 AM.
But, we're talking late
into the night last night
about what would it take to
create a truly world class
educational, learning space.
Of the kind, 3Blue1Brown
does for science and math.
But for anything.
And it was so clear to me, while
talking to him, that what's
unique is his brilliance of
how and his taste for what
is the right way to deconstruct
a really technical topic
and really understand it
from the first principles.
And I would say the true
magic of frontier research
is distilling the insight
of somebody who's really
world class at what they
do and being able to share
that with the world.
And RL is just one
technique to get there.
I think we'll invent
many other techniques.
OK.
Making sense?
Yes.
Oh my God guys.
Thank you.
Now compute.
This is the exciting
stuff for me.
I'm a computer nerd.
I'm an infrastructure nerd.
As I talked about
earlier, I studied
both economics and computer
science and statistics
and bio-informatics.
And I love the intersection of
multiple domains and compute
and infrastructure is
really where a lot of that
comes together.
How long do we have?
A quick time check.
30 minutes.
OK.
Where's Anthony?
Anthony's last year.
Dice, can you keep
me honest and give me
a heads up when we
have 10 minutes left?
OK thank you.
So, what is the big
idea with scaling?
It's that scaling
works predictably.
Capabilities scale
predictably with compute.
This is a set of
public estimates
that overlay Anthropic's revenue
over the last four years.
Correlated with the amount of
compute that they brought up
at the company.
What do you notice?
Anyone notice something
about the shape of the curve?
Exponential.
Every time.
I wouldn't even go, I
wouldn't go that far.
I wouldn't say it's
exponential actually.
It is correlated strongly
with the compute.
It's predictable.
Every time the company
brought up new compute,
roughly 60 or 90
days later, there
was a capabilities jump
and then a revenue jump.
That is quite special.
Dollar in, dollar out,
dollar of compute in,
dollar of hard assets.
Land, power, shell, which
in the financial markets,
usually trade at 3
to 4 times revenue.
Being turned into a dollar
of software revenue,
which usually trades at
30 to 40 times revenue.
From a systems perspective,
what's going on?
We have developed
a predictable way
to transform one input
into another, predictably,
that humanity considers a lot
more valuable than the input.
The output here is
roughly 10 times more
valuable to the world, to
the markets than the input.
Remember, this class is
called Frontier Systems?
We stopped calling it Security
at Scale and Infrastructure
at Scale for a reason,
because we are now
in the full stack rewrite.
And I need you guys to
start thinking up and down
the stack, not just as
engineers, not just as
or computer scientists
or electrical engineers.
I need you to start thinking
like full stack thinkers.
Think about the capital markets.
Think about the business.
Because if you want to keep
sustainably doing research
at the frontier, you've got to
run the whole loop, run it back.
So what's an example
of that in production?
If you look under
the hood Cloud Code,
these are commits that the
agent has been making publicly
on GitHub.
Beautifully correlated
with the compute buildout.
So this is not just revenue.
Somebody asked, I think
last time, Anj, is
this just like revenue pumping?
This is real usage.
Sure over here there's
probably some verbose cloud,
commits, overeager commits.
But by and large, this trend
has been pretty reliable
over the last four years.
And so even if you
took revenue out
and you just looked
at usage, this
is very real fast growing
exponential usage in coding.
For this reason,
what I've called
the Great Transition
in Infrastructure,
started last year.
Once this predictable
scaling, not just
of capabilities but of revenue
of this infrastructure trade
became legible to
the capital markets.
Everything changed.
Over the last three years, the
five largest tech companies
have decided to spend more on
infrastructure, land, power,
shell, than they have in the
preceding 30 years combined.
Last year, I think,
spent $300 billion.
This year they're going
to spend $600 billion.
Next year, they've announced
in their earnings reports,
they're going to spend
$1.2 trillion on CapEx.
These numbers are kind
of hard to fathom.
So what happens?
What happens when all the
big boys start spending?
What do you do?
Step one.
Acknowledge reality.
For the last four
years, I have lost
count of the number of
times people have called me
and said, why are you spending
all this time on compute?
It's a commodity.
Just give the
company some money.
They're going to be able to
rent from GCP, AWS and so on.
That's how the world works.
Not quite.
This is a chart that
we've been aggregating
at AMP of GPU rental
prices quarter
by quarter across a
number of estimates.
We have an internal
system we call
the AMP grid, whose job it
is, to try and understand
what's going on
in infrastructure
and try to forecast
intelligently
so that our teams and our
companies that we work with,
can get a bit of
a empirical view
on where infrastructure
is going.
What do you observe about the
price trend of H100 prices?
A chip that's over
two years old.
Over the last 90 days.
Somebody come on.
Yes?
Thank you.
Going up.
It's pretty simple.
Anybody.
Who's told you
chips or commodit,
should probably get a
phone call from you,
and ask them what
they think about this.
Because chip prices
are not going down.
They're going up.
Two years ago, when I was
calling friends at Clouds Up
and trying to rent
them for our teams,
the average H100 price
per hour was $1.73.
This morning.
I got a friend message
and say, can we give her
a quick round of applause?
The reason I'm doing
that is because you're
going to be thanking him later.
Is your chief compute
intern for this class.
For your final projects, when
you need compute credits,
he's going to be
provisioning them for you.
And so if you have any bugs and
so on, please don't come to me.
Go to who are also married.
And I think met
at Stanford here.
Been married longer
than Viv and me.
were our undergrad friends,
and was my master of rituals
in Aksai.
Which I pledged mostly
to be able to date.
Viv OK.
And hes my co-founder at AMP.
So you can bother
him anytime you want.
This morning we had a
founder who's raised,
I think $700
million, $1 billion.
I wish I could show
you the screenshot.
Said we're in a compute crunch.
Yes.
Need H100s ASAP.
How many do you need and when?
Take them right now.
Price not a problem.
It's a good time to
be a drug dealer.
This is a fundamental
assumption the entire industry
has been built on.
That chips are a commodity.
All chips depreciate.
Entire publicly traded companies
are running on this assumption.
Meanwhile, here, ground
0 in Silicon Valley.
I can tell you it's a very,
very different picture
that's emerging.
So what does that mean?
I like to look at history
to get clues about where
the world is going to go.
And I'm starting to realize
that we've seen this before.
We've lived through
cycle after cycle
of the invention of new
infrastructure, general purpose
technologies, and
then you invent
ways to turn that technology
into useful products.
Steam engine.
Make cars, make shoes,
whatever it might be.
And that results, in
what is often called
the Golden Age or
the Gilded Age,
where few people who start
hoarding those resources
get to profit at scales
we've never seen before.
And I think that's
roughly where we
are relative to the
Industrial Revolution.
So what happens next?
I said, let's look at the
history of infrastructure
for some clues.
This is the econ nerd
in me coming out.
But I promise we'll bring
it back to computer science.
I just thought I'd pull some,
I asked our friend Claude
to pull some charts together.
So if there's some
wrong numbers here.
I'm not to blame,
though I guess I'm not
following my own rules here.
But with steel 1867 to 1895.
There was, if you notice
this increase in prices,
then there was
this panic of 1873
where there was a lot
of hoarding of the steel
and prices were going up.
Then suddenly there was a panic.
Oh, the steel actually
isn't worth very much.
We hoarded too much steel.
Suddenly the prices collapsed.
Super annoying for
everybody involved.
Companies go down.
People are backstabbing
each other.
Markets up and down,
wars are being fought.
Blah, blah, blah.
Eventually, as a
society, we get together
and say, OK, this isn't good.
We don't want panics.
We want stable
production of steel,
stable consumption of steel.
Let's figure this out.
And that's what results in
this plateauing of steel.
Same with fiber optics.
I'm sure everybody here is tired
of hearing the word AI bubble.
Everybody's asking about
fiber optic overbuild and all
these companies like Cisco,
Lucent, Nortel, WorldCom
are these chip
companies the same?
Why?
Because all the
economists, all the people
writing op eds in the
Wall Street Journal
are just looking at
all the same data.
Prices go up and then come down.
It's a bubble, boom,
bust, blah, blah, blah.
Same thing with DRAM.
Very violent
semiconductor cycles.
Memory was invented,
DRAM was invented.
People go, OK, this
is really important
for personal computing.
People start hoarding it.
Then something happens.
Usually it's a panic.
It's some usually, honestly,
it's not something that big.
It's some stupid news
or some world event.
There's always world
events happening,
but it triggers a panic.
And that results in
a self-fulfilling
sell off of infrastructure,
stocks, assets, supplies.
And then you get back
up when people realize,
no, actually, there's inherent
valuable technology with this.
There's new capabilities here.
We can do something with it.
And then you either
get another rise
or you have a stabilization
of that resource.
This is the Baltic Dry
Index, with shipping.
Same thing.
These slides will be up.
I'm not going to
bore you with it.
Uranium, when we were living
through the nuclear energy boom
of the 1970s.
Same thing.
And often what happens.
And with uranium,
this is very clear.
You have the intervention
of the government
to allow the stabilization
of that resource.
And so if you look
over and over again.
And this is our friend the
H100 GPU that we talked about.
Prices were dropping after
the chip came out in June,
all the way to August of 2024.
And since then they've
steadily been rising.
This is actually a bit out
of date, as they're back up.
So what does history tell us?
One infrastructure
does is cyclical.
So at least we've
got some clues.
Hopefully unless this time is
so different, which it may be
and which is what I would
encourage you to quiz
our speakers about,
because many of them
are at the frontier
of these markets.
Hopefully we as a
society can figure out
how ideally we just skip the
whole boom and bust thing.
It's not fun for anybody.
But assuming that we're at
the start of another panic run
on compute, the
question, of course,
is how do you get to the other
side as fast as possible?
So we can all start building
useful frontier labs
and projects without having to
go wait at around the corner
and bother Larry and
Sergey for compute.
Now the usual timeline.
If you just look
across the digital era
the internet and bandwidth
build outs between these cycles
is about three years, 2.8 years.
For physical infrastructure
it was 6.3 years.
And my best guess is that and
this is the thing about AI
that's so novel.
It's a combination.
AI scaling is a
combination of massive,
you have to marshal
massive physical resources
like land, power,
shell, chips to produce
this very digital thing
called software revenue.
Intelligence is bits.
But the production is atoms.
Those worlds don't
like colliding.
And that's what's new here.
And scrambling and
confusing a lot of people
is how do we actually coordinate
these two things in a way that's
stable, reliable, and so on.
The central question, of course,
is how do we get compute?
Or is compute rather
just a commodity?
That's the tension we've been
talking about over the last 15
minutes, is compute scarcity.
Is it something where
all of you should
be spending your time wondering,
should you be making chips?
Should you be making more,
better, interconnect?
Or should you be spending
time on distilling
your aesthetics, your
creativity, your intelligence?
31 blue, 1 Brown, into
how to teach the world
new kinds of science
and math and physics.
That's the core tension.
Good news is this
class covers both.
So for those of you who
are electrical engineers
and want to go into chips,
you're getting that exposure.
And for those of you who want to
be frontier model researchers,
you're going to
get that exposure.
And you can decide, OK, we're
not here to decide for you,
but here's my view on it as
one participant macro today.
Unlike electricity or coal,
compute is not fungible.
Electricity is fungible.
Megawatts or megawatts
or megawatts everywhere.
Pipe into a grid.
You get them out.
It wasn't always
the case, and I'm
going to talk about
that in a second.
But today compute
is not a commodity.
The prices are rising and
they are not fungible.
This chart shows that
there's varying prices
for different chips.
Forget chips from different
companies like AMD and NVIDIA.
Chips from the same
manufacturer are not fungible.
The H100 is different
from the GB200 which
is different from the B300.
These numbers may not
mean anything to you.
That's what I spend all day
talking about with my research
teams.
So number one, the
problem or the indicator
that compute is not a commodity
is that compute is not fungible
today.
And two, forecasting
compute at the micro level,
is very, very hard.
Unlike electricity
where we've developed
pretty stable mechanisms for
how to forecast our consumption,
barring hurricanes
and so on there.
We're generally like,
we have power here.
I grew up in rural India,
in a boarding school called
Rishi Valley, and we used to
have power outages roughly once
in the summer, like
every other week.
Today, luckily, I think they've
put a transmission, like they
built a backup generator there.
But in most parts
of the world we've
had stable forecasting
of energy and therefore
the stable production of that
energy and supply for what,
at least 75 years.
That's not the
case with compute.
Because inside of
these research labs,
one team finds it very hard
to reason about their needs.
Training is a spiky thing.
You think about, OK, how do
I create a new capability
like a frontier
model for coding?
You take an algorithm, you
play with it on small scale.
If it starts working,
then you spike up
for your hero training runs.
Inference when you
deploy your chatbot.
Turns out a lot of people,
especially if your chatbot
is deployed in the US.
A lot of people use
it during the day.
No one's using it at night.
Inference is cyclical too.
And so we're in that
part of humanity
where, not only is the most
valuable input a production
of intelligence,
not fungible, it's
also super hard to forecast.
And as a result, we have those
hoarding cycles going on.
Remember I showed you those the
big boys buying up as much land
power as they can over the
next four years going, look,
there's a pretty reliable
trade we can make, for hardware
to software revenue.
Not sure which
research, which model,
which breakthrough
will actually do that,
but we might as well
just buy it all up.
So the question I spent a lot
of time recently thinking about,
and I think you guys
should, for those of you who
are interested in
infrastructure is what did it
take in history to turn this
scarce, monopolized production
resource into a productive,
accessible commodity
for everyone who's working
or innovating in the field?
And my view is, again,
history tells us
that there's two
key things you need
to solve the fungibility
and the access problem.
One, you need
standards AC/DC right
TCP/IP the standards that we
convene on over and over again
to say this is
infrastructure to be stable.
Let's all agree on a standard
format for this infrastructure
to be produced in, so
we can all consume it
no matter where it is.
And the second is
you need institutions
to enforce those standards,
because inevitably humans
are misaligned at some
scale, and somebody needs
to coordinate and align
human beings to adopt
those standards at scale.
And that's roughly
where we are right now.
So what makes a
commodity fungible?
It's pretty simple commodity.
This is all, how many
people have taken Econ 1A?
Oh, wow.
OK.
I've got to do some
econ assignments, too.
For those of you who want
to work at the frontier.
This is a pretty standard
textbook definition
of a fungibility.
What makes a commodity fungible?
Commodity means a common unit.
It needs a standard
delivery interface.
It needs interconnection and
pooling, needs metering, control
and settlement.
And the buyers can substitute
one suppliers unit for another.
OK, you should really
understand this definition
if you intend to train any
kind of frontier models
because this is
not the case today.
So this is my point.
Technical standards and
fungibility don't come easy.
They need institutions
to enforce them,
to reallocate away power from
those who benefit from hoarding,
and instead prioritize
the public benefit.
That's what we need more and
more of in these infrastructure
cycles.
Is somebody or some
group of people
need to start stepping in
and saying good, for you.
Great.
You have enough compute.
Those folks over there don't.
Let's pool.
And let's figure out
an optimal allocation
of this resource across
society, across a country,
across the world.
That's what we call
the public benefit.
Yeah.
10 minutes.
OK, perfect.
I will try to zip through this.
We're almost at the end, so
the punchline is pretty simple.
We are in the
pre-standardization
of compute era.
If you just look at
all the previous cycles
railroads from 1886.
Electrification in 1907.
Telephone, aviation,
internet, semiconductors,
new general purpose technology.
Huge explosion in infrastructure
needs usually consolidation
amongst three or four players.
Sometimes industries
step in and self-regulate
and they come up with standards
if they can get along.
Other times a government
or an institution
has to come in and say,
these are the standards.
And we're at that moment
roughly in history for compute.
So food for thought
for this quarter.
This is your assignment and
there'll be some readings.
But I'd like you to keep this
at the back of your minds.
One, what will it take to ensure
a peaceful transition on compute
over the next couple of years?
And two, what is
your part in this?
You can be a part of this
change because remember, I
said at the start
of this lecture,
you are extraordinarily lucky to
be alive at this moment in time.
It may not be clear to you.
And it's easier to connect
the dots in hindsight.
But think of yourselves
not just as students,
but as active participants.
And part of the goal and design
of the project this quarter
is to try to make you
more and more active
participants in this stack.
You can blog, you can
tweet, you can write,
you can share your thoughts
with the world on what
are the standards you wish
emerge so that your job could
be easier.
And hopefully,
some of the people
in this room who
are going to come
talk to you, who are running
many of these institutions who
can help evangelize
these standards,
adopt them, coordinate them.
We'll hear from you.
Cool.
All right.
That's all I've got.
I have a bonus.
This is from last year.
This is a screenshot
of RTX 5090 prices
in USD over the last 18 months.
Who knows what RTX 5090 is?
OK, cool.
Some gamers in the audience.
This is NVIDIA's gaming chip.
It was also the grand prize
for the best project last year
when Jensen came by.
He signed five 1590s.
I think this is whose team made
a really cool gaming product
and pretty valuable chip.
So I'm not going to ask Jensen
this time for more 1590s
because they're a little bit
more valuable this time around.
But we'll see.
Maybe there'll be surprises.
OK thank you guys.